(Howard:)Uh, so, this Glenn guy.
(Howard:)You say you went out with
him for, like, a year.
(Bernadette:)Do we really need to talk
about my old boyfriend now?
(Howard:)No. I guess not.
(Howard:)What is he, like,
six-four, six-five?
(Bernadette:)Six-seven.
(Howard:)Probably has a hard time
finding a suit that fits.
(Bernadette:)Is something
bothering you?
(Howard:)No. It's just...
What?
(Howard:)I'm just thinking.
(Howard:)If you had sex with that guy,
(Howard:)I mean, there's nothing
I can do here
(Howard:)that will make
any kind of... impact.
(Bernadette:)Howard, it's not a contest.
(Bernadette:)I love you.
I want to be with you.
(Howard:)Yeah, great, love you, too,
but...
(Howard:)If it were a contest,
(Howard:)I wouldn't have a chance, right?
(Bernadette:)You can't think
that way.
(Howard:)Yep.
(Howard:)Loser.
(Bernadette:)Howard, stop it.
(Howard:)Sorry. I just
never figured that
(Howard:)a guy like me going out
with a girl like you